I've learned one thing.
Shaking people down for points
isn't Hosen's only motive.
What do you mean?
I thought Hosen wouldn't
let his people pair up for anything
but large numbers of points
because he wanted to stock
up points for himself.
But if that were the case,
he'd be more proactive
about partnering up the
lower-scoring students.
That is true.
Any student who fails suffers
a painful point penalty.
You're right, Ayanokoji-senpai.
Hosen-kun hasn't taken any
payment from our classmates.
He just wants to impose rules to keep
an iron grip on the class, then?
And any students who break
those rules are ostracized.
But relationships forged with points
will always be dependent on points.
I want to build a relationship of
trust from an even playing field.
Take my offer to Hosen-kun.
I'm prepared to discuss at any time.
Very well. I'll call him and see.
I have Hosen-kun on the phone.
Heya. Nanase filled me in.
I'd prefer to speak in person.
Hosen Kazuomi
Nah, we're not doing that.
So you refuse to even negotiate?
That's right.
But Hosen-kun—
Hosen Kazuomi
Shut your damn trap.
Where do you get off talking back to me?
I'll kill you.
I'd rather you didn't.
I'd like you to meet with
Horikita-senpai, though.
Hosen Kazuomi
Next time you contact me,
you better have the points I asked for.
Call Ended
I'm sorry!
Don't bow to us, please.
I'm very grateful for
the help you've offered.
But...
At the very least, I've made my
intentions clear to Hosen-kun.
That's enough for now.
Classroom of the Elite 4th Season 2nd Year 1st Term
#3 Determination of a Leader
Calling
In Call
Took you long enough to pick up!
Sorry.
Did you look into the thing
I asked you for this morning?
Yeah, that's why I'm calling.
The clerk I talked to said they'd only
sold one since the start of April.
Apparently, some first-year
tried to buy one,
but after they checked out, some other
kid talked to them, and they returned it.
Who was the student who
asked them to return it?
The clerk didn't know.
Said it was a girl, though.
Did my intel help you out?
Yes, even more than I expected.
I'm pretty good at stuff, huh?
Better show me some gratitude.
I am grateful.
By the way, how are your studies going?
Well, I mean...
Look, you haven't been to
the study group lately, have you?
Would you be more motivated
if I were there?
Well, yeah!
I gotta show off my best side
when my boyfriend's there.
Then will you come to
my apartment tomorrow?
You wanna hang out?!
Yes, but we won't be hanging out.
We'll be studying.
Koenji-kun.
You haven't found a partner yet, I hear.
What of it?
I'll easily achieve a passing grade
no matter who my partner is.
Would you let me pick your partner, then?
I must refuse.
Why?
Because I am who I am!
Is that everything?
I suppose. For now.
I-I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Did something happen?
I was trying to convince
Hosen-kun to come with me.
It seems you didn't succeed.
We'll have to resort to
more forceful methods.
We're not making any progress like this.
May I offer an idea of my own, then?
I've determined that Hosen-kun's methods
will hurt our competitiveness
moving forward.
As a desperate last resort,
I'm thinking about making a play
to become leader of Class 1-D.
Are you serious?
Wouldn't that put too much
of the burden on you?
I don't mind.
I don't want to lose the trust and
opportunities you're offering me.
Going against Hosen-kun won't
just hurt your class's unity.
It'll tear it in half.
I can't let you do that.
I suppose that's true.
Class 1-D's problems will be resolved if
we can just get Hosen-kun on our side.
So will you help me change his mind?
It's a dangerous gamble.
I'm aware of that.
I also believe there's a very good
chance that we could work together.
Despite how hostile he's being to you?
I've chosen to interpret that
as sublimated affection.
For now, at least.
I also think that convincing
Hosen-kun is the best way.
If you'll trust me with this,
I'll make sure he meets with you
by Sunday, two days from now.
I trust you.
I look forward to seeing
you both in two days.
Yes, we'll be there.
What is it?
Time for my study group.
We have our game plan.
Can you handle the rest?
Sure.
Horikita-senpai seems
to be juggling a lot.
To lead a class, I guess
that's what you have to do.
Horikita-senpai is your class's leader.
But...
What kind of person are
you, Ayanokoji-senpai?
I think that you might be a
rather base and wicked person.
What do you mean by that?
Well...
The White Room student would want
to scrutinize me from up close.
To prove that they're better... and...
to prove themselves to that man.
But that didn't seem like something you'd
say to a fellow White Room student.
I'm sorry. Pretend I didn't say anything.
Goodbye, Senpai. I'll be going now.
Nanase.
Are you aware of the existence
of protection points?
No, I'm not.
You can spend them to negate an expulsion.
Why are you telling me about this?
As thanks for your help.
I appreciate that.
There's a lot of people
around outside at this time,
but I was really careful not to be seen.
Okay, let's get started.
Huh?! Shouldn't there
be something else first?
If your studies are where they should be,
I'll happily entertain
whatever chit-chat you'd like.
Hey, question.
Your Academic Achievement
rating is C, right?
But you could get a better
score if you wanted, right?
I suppose.
Why go so hard to hide it, then?
I didn't want to stand out.
So, hey! What score would you
get if you went all-out?
400.
For real? But isn't that...
Since coming here, I haven't encountered
a single problem I couldn't solve.
Let's get started, then.
You sit here.
Teach me by my side.
Huh?
What's this?
Hair, I guess.
It's a red hair! And it's long!
This clearly belongs to a girl!
Red hair! A girl I've never seen before!
Yes?
Oh? Isn't this Ayanokoji-senpai's
apartment?
Sorry, it's me.
How can I help you?
Oh, you have a guest?
Should I come back another time?
No, it's fine. Come on in.
Thanks for having me!
Hey there! I'm Amasawa Ichika!
A pleasure.
You're a second-year, right?
What's your name?
Karuizawa Kei.
Karuizawa-senpai, huh?
Hey, are you Ayanokoji-senpai's
girlfriend or something?
How's that your business?!
And just what is your
relationship to Kiyotaka?
I'll explain all that in a bit.
I think I may have left
something at your apartment.
It's one of my favorite hair ties.
What?!
Pretty sure I took it off
somewhere around here...
Maybe it slid under something...
Senpai, this might get a little lurid.
I'll look.
Hey. I want an answer to my question.
Let's see, how should I put it...
Ayanokoji-senpai has become my...
personal chef?
What in the world?!
She's Sudo's partner.
I cooked for her once.
Why were you cooking
for Sudo-kun's partner?
I'll check in the kitchen.
You keep searching there.
Got it.
Excuse me!
Like she said, I had her
over once and cooked.
That's all.
That's really all?!
I'm gonna see if she—
There it is!
It must've slipped under the fridge.
Looks like I'm a third wheel,
so I'd better be going!
Sorry to make you go out of your way.
No prob. See ya later!
Still, you're quite a smooth operator.
I didn't expect you to have
such a pretty girlfriend.
But I guess I shouldn't have
you cooking for me alone, then.
You bet he shouldn't!
You should join us next time,
Karuizawa-senpai.
Bye-bye, then!
You seem quite close with your
pretty little kohai, Kiyotaka.
105 pairs have now formed.
That's close to 70%.
If the White Room student
is among the remainder,
there's a good chance we'll be paired up.
Well, well.
If it isn't Ayanokoji-kun.
Sakayanagi.
You've been quite assertive with the
first-years lately, haven't you?
I'm just working with Horikita to find
partners for the likes of Sudo and Ike.
I see.
But is that really all it is?
What do you mean?
It's my understanding that the White Room
sent an assassin to have you expelled.
I'll be fine.
May I ask why you're so sure?
I'm going to discard my previous approach.
I'm not going to hold anything
back from now on.
I see.
If you haven't found a partner yet,
would you like my assistance?
That's very considerate of you.
But I'll have to turn you down.
You don't trust my judgment?
I acknowledge your skill.
But I'll decide my destiny for myself.
I see.
I'll give you some space, then.
I'll watch your battle
from a distance instead.
Hey, you got a minute?
You're Ayanokoji-senpai
of Class 2-D, aren't you?
I'm Utomiya of Class 1-C.
This is Tsubaki.
We were wondering if we could talk
to you about being her partner.
I'm sorry it's so sudden,
but would you hear us out?
I hate being in another person's debt,
or having others in mine.
I want a relationship
I won't regret later.
I'm curious about something. May I?
Of course.
How many people did you ask before me?
I'm sorry. You're actually the first.
Out of everyone,
it just happened to be me?
That's accurate,
but there's also a reason.
We think the Class A and C second-years
might request private points.
I see. That does make sense.
I don't have a partner yet,
but I have a candidate in mind.
We're still working out the details.
I see.
I guess that's too bad.
It'd be faster to find someone else, then.
True.
Here. This is my contact information.
This may be rather self-serving,
but if I can't work things out with
my partner, I may contact you again.
Understood.
Let's go, Tsubaki.
Tsubaki Sakurako and Utomiya Riku.
I'll have to keep those names in mind.
Sorry, Karuizawa-san,
to call you out so suddenly.
Hey, it's all good.
What did you wanna talk about?
Why... did you break up with Hirata-kun?
Oh, I didn't tell you?
You did, but...
It didn't really make sense to me.
When you broke up...
Was it because you wanted something else?
Huh? Where's that coming from?
I dunno what you're talking about.
Karuizawa-san...
Are you dating Ayanokoji-kun?
You are, aren't you?!
H-Hang on, what makes you think that?
Have you been after him since I asked
you to help me get together with him?
Have you loved him since before then?
H-Hang on a minute here—
Be honest!
If you don't, I won't be able to
think of you as a friend anymore.
Well...
You're right.
Aya—
I mean, Kiyotaka and I are dating.
You even call him Kiyotaka...
We started dating at the
end of spring break.
Just a little before then, actually.
My main question is,
how long have you liked him?
I dunno.
But... I started to around the time
you were asking me for advice.
I see.
You're mad, right?
I don't love it.
You knew how I felt and
went behind my back.
But he already blew me off, so it's
not like I have any right to be mad...
Still...
Can we say we're even now, Karuizawa-san?
You wanna give me one
more for good measure?
N-No... I don't think I'm
brave enough for that.
And... I'm sorry for hitting you.
Hey, no problem.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I fell in love with the person you like.
Well, of course you did.
Ayanokoji-kun's really cool.
He's way hotter than Hirata-kun.
Hey!
What are you doing, Karuizawa-san?
I really am sorry.
Sunday night.
It's the time Nanase designated
for us to meet with Hosen.
Hey.
How's test prep coming?
Great, of course!
I'm betting I'll score a 250 at least!
Seems like you enjoy studying now.
Hell no.
But getting praise from Suzune
is pretty motivating, y'know?
Hey, Ayanokoji.
If I asked Suzune out sometime soon,
you think she'd give me the go-ahead?
I don't think so.
Yeah, I figured.
I've caused a hell of a
lot of trouble for her.
For the rest of the class, too.
A little effort now ain't gonna
make up for all the crap I've caused.
But for the next two years,
I'm gonna improve on my strengths
and try to bolster my
weaknesses as much as I can.
And by the time we graduate, I'll be a
guy who can actually help the class out.
What if, after all that work,
Horikita still doesn't
return your feelings?
Will you hate studying again?
I'll wanna die and feel
like I wanna punch someone.
But I'd be letting her
down if I did that, right?
That's the one thing I don't want.
I'm here.
Shall we?
That snotty little first-year, Hosen...
You really think you can
get him on our side?
I wouldn't be here if I didn't.
Sudo-kun, don't say
anything rash, all right?
I wasn't gonna!
Senpai, sorry we're late.
Outta the way, Nanase.